<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Jeboira</title><link>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Jeboira</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:16:08 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advent of Code Day 3</title><link>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/aoc3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:16:08 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/aoc3/</guid><description>On the third day of advent of code, the problems got more difficult, and this is where we get into problems that may not be just purely easy, the last two days were fairly stright forward as day one was just an array question and day 2 was a stack question, now day 3 is somewhat of an array question but if you can find an optimal solution or not is another thing entirely.</description></item><item><title>Advent of Code Day 2</title><link>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/advent-of-code2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 21:03:16 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/advent-of-code2/</guid><description>Advent of code day 2 was actually easier than the first day in my opinion as the first day required you to use brain for more advanced array based approach on day 2 it was simply just a stack machine.
Part 1 So all you have to do is read in the inputs and parse them based on the criteria that is presented in the prompt. step 1 is to read in the file contents and pase all the funny instructions and numbers.</description></item><item><title>Advent of Code Day 1</title><link>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/advent-of-code/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 05:04:08 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://loganlieou.github.io/website/posts/advent-of-code/</guid><description>Yes I will start to write about this and explain my reasoning and code that I wrote for this year&amp;rsquo;s advent of code right now the website just existing because I would like my website to respawn thank you very much.
Reading in Files The first step and the first step to almost every AoC challenge is to read in the contents of a file to do this in julia simply:</description></item></channel></rss>